<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zoo Directory</string>
    <string name="lion">Lion</string>
    <string name="croc">Crocodile</string>
    <string name="koala">Koala</string>
    <string name="fruit">Fruit Bat</string>
    <string name="silverback">Silverback Gorilla</string>
    <string name="lion_facts">Lions generally all live within the Sahara desert in Africa, although some live in India. Male lions grow impressive manes the older they get. These manes grow up to 16cm long and are a sign of dominance. The older they get, the darker their manes go. Lions are highly adaptable and can live in very dry areas like the Kalahari Desert. Here they get most of their water from their prey and will even drink from plants such as the Tsamma melon. Lions do most of their hunting at night as their eyes have adapted to the dark and this gives them a huge advantage over their prey.</string>
    <string name="croc_facts">Crocodiles are large reptiles found in regions of Africa, Asia, the Americas, and Australia. There are 13 Crocodile species including the Dwarf Crocodile, which is the smallest. Crocodiles are carnivores that will feast on fish, birds, and frogs. Occasionally, they will cannibalize each other. In order to eat their food, crocs will clamp down on their prey, crush them with a jaw pressure of 3700 pounds per square inch. If an animal is struggling while they are trying to eat it, crocs will then perform what is called a death roll, which shocks and stuns their prey, allowing them to feast. </string>
    <string name="koala_facts">Koala\'s aren\'t bears, even though they are generally called Koala bears. However, they are in fact marsupials, and share more characteristics with animals like wombats. Baby Koalas, called Joeys, will develop in their mother\'s pouch for about six months. Afterwards, they will ride on their mom\'s back for another six months, while only using the pouch to eat and sleep. Koalas are found only in Australia and are a national symbol of their wildlife. Koalas will only eat eucalyptus leaves and can eat up to a kilogram a day. Koalas also aren\'t very active, so they will sleep for up to 18 hours a day.</string>
    <string name="fruit_facts">Fruit Bats are one of the largest species of bats in the world. They are often referred to as a frugivore because the thrive on raw fruits. They have also been called flying foxes because their heads look like fox heads. Fruit bats are generally located in a very humid environment which is why here at this zoo and others, you will generally feel very humid, and will start sweating when you walk into their exhibits. Fruit Bats will also live up to about 15 years total. </string>
    <string name="silverback_facts">Silverback Gorillas are male mountain gorillas that live in the Democratic Republic of Congo, Rwanda, and Uganda. They live in wo isolated groups, with one living in the Virunga Volcanoes, and the others living in Bwindi Impenetrable National Park. Humans share about 98% of their DNA with Gorillas. This means exposure to a human illness can have a detrimental impact on gorillas. Gorillas are the biggest and most powerful living primates, weighing up to 180 kg. They can also grow as tall as 5 foot 5. Gorillas spend about a quarter of their day eating. Their diet consists of leaves, snails, ants, and bark.</string>
</resources>